{
    "subject": "resource/Mikhail_Gurevich_(aircraft_designer)",
    "predicate": "ontology/discipline",
    "object": "resource/Aerospace_engineering",
    "human_readable": "Mikhail Gurevich (aircraft designer) is a specialist in aerospace engineering.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9269431829452515,
            "question": "What field of engineering is Mikhail Gurevich a specialist in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8538423776626587,
            "question": "What is Mikhail Gurevich's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8532904386520386,
            "question": "Is Mikhail Gurevich involved in the design of airplanes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7304404973983765,
            "question": "What industry does Mikhail Gurevich work in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7251343727111816,
            "question": "What type of designs is Mikhail Gurevich known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6634868383407593,
            "question": "What are some challenges that aircraft designers like Mikhail Gurevich face?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6492580771446228,
            "question": "What is the primary focus of Mikhail Gurevich's expertise?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6093019843101501,
            "question": "What types of projects might Mikhail Gurevich be involved in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.484397292137146,
            "question": "What does 'aerospace engineering' involve?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32500335574150085,
            "question": "How could Mikhail Gurevich's work impact society?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Mikhail Gurevich (aircraft designer) is a specialist in aerospace engineering.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6031_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What does 'aerospace engineering' involve?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6031_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What types of projects might Mikhail Gurevich be involved in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6031_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the primary focus of Mikhail Gurevich's expertise?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6031_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6031_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6031_115.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6031_141.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6031_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6031_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6031_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6031_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6031_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6031_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6031_65.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide information about Mikhail Gurevich's education and career, which include his studies in mathematics and aeronautical engineering. Additionally, he worked as an engineer of the state company \"Heat and Power\" and later became a designer team leader and Chief Designer at Mikoyan-Gurevich Design Bureau. These facts support the claim that Mikhail Gurevich is a specialist in aerospace engineering."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Mikhail Gurevich's background and career, which includes his education in aeronautical engineering and his work as an aircraft designer. This supports the statement that he is a specialist in aerospace engineering."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}